Guide to the Clifton R. Merritt Papers 1935-2008
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- The American Wilderness Alliance / American Wildlands, 1957-2007; Series IV; 29.5 linear feet
  - Administration, 1965-2007; Subseries 1; 5 linear feet
    - Board Meetings, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 53/23-24)
    - Board Meetings, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 53/25)
    - Board Members, 1987 (Box-folder 53/26)
    - Board Members, 1997 (Box-folder 53/27)
    - Board Memos, Meeting Notes, 1992 (Box-folder 53/28)
    - Board of Directors and Executive Director Memos and Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Board of Directors Manual and Meeting Minutes, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Board of Directors Memos and Internal Documents, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Board of Directors Memos and Internal Documents, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 54/4-5)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1987 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Board of Trustees Memos, Correspondence, Notes, and Internal Documents, 1976-1997 (Box-folder 54/7-10)
    - Board of Trustees Packet for Board Meetings, 1992 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, Northern Regional Office Issues, and Development Information, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Leslie Buckmaster, Resume, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Budget Projections and Financial Reports, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Bullitt Foundation, 1993 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Dale Burk, Resume and Vitae, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - By-Laws, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Dan Chandler, Resume, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Charter Members #1, 1978 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Cinnabar Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Cinnabar Foundation-Annual Report and Grants, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 55/11-13)
    - Clifton Merritt Internal Documents, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 55/14-15)
    - Conferences, 1996-2007 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Conservation Endowment Fund, John Taft, 1987 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Consultants and Advisory Councils, 1993 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Corporate Certificate of Authority, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Lance Craighead, Resume, 1997 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - CS Fund, 1986 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Bill Cunningham, Resume, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Directories, American Wildlands and Affiliates, 1998 and undated (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Directory, Board of Trustees and Staff, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Duties and Responsibilities of Associate Executive Director, 1986 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Duties and Responsibilities of Montana Field Representatives and Natural Resources Specialist, undated (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Economic Inventory Grant Proposal-Big Hole, Montana, undated (Box-folder 56/12)
    - Employment Inquiries, 1987 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Executive Director Search, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Executive Director's Manual, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Expense Claims, 1988 (Box-folder 56/16)
    - Expenses, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 56/17)
    - Expenses, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 56/18)
    - Financial Reports, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 56/19-21)
    - Financials, 1985 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Financials, 1986 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Jim Frain, Resume, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Paul Fritz, Idaho Representative, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Paul Fritz, Personnel, 1987 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Fund Raising, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Fund Raising, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Funding, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Funding, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Funding File, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - General Office Procedures, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - Goals and Objectives, undated (Box-folder 57/12)
    - Grant and Funding Proposals, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 57/13)
    - Grant Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Grant Status, 1994 (Box-folder 57/15)
    - Dan Heinz, Resume, undated (Box-folder 57/16)
    - History of American Wildlands, 1994 (Box-folder 57/17)
    - Robert Hitchcock, Resume, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 57/18)
    - Internal Documents, 1978-2001 (Box-folder 57/19)
    - Internal Memos, organizational history, and board meeting minutes, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Internal Revenue Service Letter, 1978 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - IRS Exemption Letter, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Job Descriptions, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Ken Knapp, Director of Development, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Jeff Larmer, Resume, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Letterhead and Artwork, 1994 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Dave McCargo, Resume, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Membership Brochure, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - Membership Information, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - Membership Letters, 1965-1994 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - Membership Lists, 1989 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Membership Reference Materials, 1965-1981 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - Membership Solicitation, 1987 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Memos and Internal Documents, 1994-2005 (Box-folder 58/15-16)
    - Clifton Merritt, Background Sketches, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Clifton Merritt, Expense Claims, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Clifton Merritt, Expenses, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Clifton Merritt, Meeting Notes, 1990-1997 and undated (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Clifton Merritt, Personal, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - Clifton Merritt, Personnel, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Clifton Merritt, Resume, 1979-1998 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Clifton Merritt, Resume, 1987 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - Clifton Merritt, Vitae and Biographical Information, 1978-1997 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - Mission and Vision, 1994 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Montana Contributions, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - Montana Field Office Grant Proposal to Montana Outfitters and Guides, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Montana Grant Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 59/13)
    - Montana Mailing Lists, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 59/14)
    - Montana Solicitation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 59/15)
    - Montana Wilderness Association, Friends of the Bitterroot, and American Wildlands Bitterroot Lawsuit, 2001 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Monthly Activity Reports, Bozeman Offices, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Carla Neasel, Development Director, Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - New Choices-Funding Submission and Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - New Land Foundation-Grant Proposal, 1996 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - New/Renew Membership Contributions, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Organization Planning, 1997 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Patagonia Foundation, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Patagonia Grant, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Personnel, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Personnel Policies, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Personnel Policies-Revised, 1994 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - Pledge Program, 1987 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Potential Applicants, 1997 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - Dr. Thomas Power, Resource Economist, Resume, 1993 (Box-folder 60/15)
    - Program Plan, 1997 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Program Plans, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Purposes and Functions Advisory Council, undated (Box-folder 60/18)
    - Purposes and Functions-Board of Trustees, undated (Box-folder 60/19)
    - Range Management Policy Reform Program and Grant Proposal, 1993 (Box-folder 60/20)
    - Range Management Policy Reform Program and Grant Proposal, 1994 (Box-folder 60/21)
    - Sally Ranney, Correspondence, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Reports from the Director, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Resumes for Executive Director, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 61/3-5)
    - Resumes of the Board, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Roadless Area Mailers, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Brooke Russell, Resume, 1995 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Ruth Mott Fund-Grant Proposal, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Ruth Mott Fund-Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Special Appeals Letters, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Staff Reports and Memos, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Tatshenshini-Board Meeting, 1993 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Testimonials, 1994 (Box-folder 61/15)
    - Darcy Tickner, Resume, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Time Sheets and Lobby Reports, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Vanguard Brochures and Information, 1987 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Vanguard Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 62/4-5)
    - Vanguard Letter, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Vanguard Letter #1, 1986 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Vanguard Letter #2, 1986 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Vanguard Letter #3, 1986 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Vanguard Letter #4, 1987 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Vanguard Membership Renewal, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Vanguard Proposal, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Vanguard Solicitation-Follow Up, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Wage Slips, 1980 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Richard Walker, Resume, 1996 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Don Whittemore and Dawn Amato, Resumes, 1989 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Wild Country Fund Endowment, 1994 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Wild Country Vanguard, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Wild Country Vanguard Letter, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Wilderness Vanguard, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Robert Williams, Resume, 1989 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - John Wright, Resume, 1991 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Year-End Fundraising Letters, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Dennis Zadra, Resume, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 63/10)
  - Subject Files, 1957-2007; Subseries 2; 20.5 linear feet
    - Absaroka-Beartooth Wilderness, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Absaroka-Beartooth Wilderness, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Acreages added to the Wilderness System in 1984, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - Ad Hoc Northern Rockies Wildlands Steering Committee, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - Adam's Rib Proposal-Colorado, 1987 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Adventure Travel Society, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Alaska, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63/17)
    - Alaska, 1992-2005 (Box-folder 63/18)
    - Alaska Fish and Wildlife-Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 63/19)
    - Alaska Fish and Wildlife-General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 63/20)
    - Alaska Fish and Wildlife-Service News, 1987 (Box-folder 63/21)
    - Alaska Lands Bill, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 63/22)
    - Alaska National Interest Lands, 1980 (Box-folder 63/23)
    - Alaska National Interest Lands Conservation Act (ANILCA), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 63/24)
    - Alaska Oil and Gas Lease Appeal, 1994 (Box-folder 63/25)
    - Alice Creek Area, 1997 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Allan Mountain-Bitterroot National Forest, 1974-1997 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Allan Mountain (Colter-Shields) Area-Sula Ranger District, 1988 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies, 1991-2004 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies Newsletter, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies Newsletter, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies-Grizzly Bear Recovery, 1998 (Box-folder 64/8)
    - Alternative Wilderness-Montana, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 64/9)
    - American Land Conservation Award-Dick Carter, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - American Pioneer Skills Award, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - American Trails Network, 1987 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - American Wilderness Adventures, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - Anaconda-Pintler Wilderness, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - Anaconda-Pintler Wilderness Additions, 1993 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - Ancient Forest Legislation, 1992 (Box-folder 64/16)
    - Appeals and Litigation, 1994 (Box-folder 64/17)
    - Appeals, etc.-Dan Heinz-Montana and Colorado, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 65/1-2)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 65/4-5)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1987 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge-Alaska Coalition, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Arizona, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Arrow Ranch, Jim Welch, 1987 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Articles, Clifton R. Merritt, 1958-1995 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Aspen Wilderness Workshop, 1983 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Audubon Wild Country Program, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - Badger-Two Medicine Roadless Area, 1984 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Badger-Two Medicine Roadless Area, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Badger-Two Medicine Roadless Area, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Baucus, Max, Correspondence Regarding Legislation, 1990-2003 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Bear News Publications, 1995 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Beartooth Wildlife Management Area, 2002 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Beaverhead National Forest, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Beaverhead National Forest Land Use Planning, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Below-Cost Timber Sales, undated (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Below-Cost Timber Sales, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Benefits and Costs of the United States Forest Service in Colorado, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Best of the West, 1987 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - Big Belt Mountains, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - Big Creek Lake-Comments on Permanent Storage Shed, 2003 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - Big Open Project, 2002 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - Big Snowies Wilderness Study Area, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - Big Snowy Mountains-Wilderness Study Area-Lewis and Clark National Forest, 2001 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - Big Wild Action Report, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - Big Wild Advocates, 1999 (Box-folder 66/19)
    - Big Wild Advocates, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 66/20)
    - Big Wild Advocates, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 66/21)
    - Bitter Creek, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 66/22)
    - Bitter Creek Wilderness Study Area, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 66/23)
    - Bitter Creek Wilderness Study Area and Mixed-Grass Prairie, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 66/24)
    - Bitterroot Forest Plan Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Bitterroot National Forest, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Bitterroot National Forest, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Bitterroot National Forest-Appeal, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Bitterroot National Forest-Comments on the Burned Area Recovery Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Bitterroot National Forest-Fiscal Year 1995 Monitoring and Evaluation Report, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Bitterroot National Forest-Projects, 1999 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Bitterroot National Forest-Wilderness Issues, 1995-2007 (Box-folder 67/8-9)
    - Bitterroot Wilderness Proposals, 1971-2002 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Black Hills National Forest, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Black Ridge Canyons and Black Ridge Canyons West Wilderness Study Area, 1987 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Blackfoot River-Montana, 1998 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - Blue Joint and Sapphire Wilderness, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - Blue Joint Wilderness Study Area, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 67/15)
    - Bob Marshall, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 67/16)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness Area-Fish and Wildlife Plan, 1988 (Box-folder 67/17)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness Complex Newsletters, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 67/18)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness Study Area, 1981 (Box-folder 67/19)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness-Gas and Oil, 1979-1993 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Bob Marshall Wilderness-General Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Boggs, Denise, Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 68/3-4)
    - Buffalo Campaign, 2000 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Bunker Creek Issue-Flathead National Forest, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Bureau of Land Management, 1985 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Bureau of Land Management, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Bureau of Land Management, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Bureau of Land Management Action Taken on Wilderness Study Areas, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 68/10-12)
    - Bureau of Land Management Fact Sheet, 1984 (Box-folder 68/13)
    - Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Proposals-Montana, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 68/14)
    - Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Study Area Permits, 1987 (Box-folder 68/15)
    - Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Study Areas, 1988 (Box-folder 69/1-2)
    - Bureau of Land Management Wilderness/Primitive Areas, 1988 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - Bureau of Land Management-Oil and Gas, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Conrad Burns, Correspondence Regarding Legislation, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Senator Conrad Burns, Wilderness, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Butte District Bureau of Land Management, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - California, 1987 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - California Big Horn Sheep, 1987 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - California Desert Protection Act, 1987 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Canada, 1987 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - Cascade Holistic Economic Consultants, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 69/12)
    - Celebrate America's Rivers Conference, undated (Box-folder 69/13)
    - Centennial Mountains Wilderness Study Area, 1999 (Box-folder 69/14)
    - Center for Public Integrity, 1994 (Box-folder 69/15)
    - Central Montana Guides and Wilderness, 1988 (Box-folder 69/16)
    - Central Rockies Wilderness Issues, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 69/17-18)
    - Charles M. Russell National Wildlife Refuge, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 69/19)
    - Charles M. Russell Wildlife Range, 1994 (Box-folder 69/20)
    - Chevron Conservation Awards Program, 1988 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Chief Joseph Wildlands, 1993 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Clif Merritt and Wilderness Wildlife: Learning How to Live in Paradise, Robert N. Baker Thesis Drafts, 2005 (Box-folder 70/3-4)
    - Clippings, 1957-1981 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Coalition for Conservation of Colorado Fisheries, 1994 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Colorado Forest Service Wilderness Bills-Colorado National Forest Wilderness Act, 1980 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Colorado National Forest Wilderness Act of 1979, S.2123, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - Colorado National Forest Wilderness-General Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Colorado Outdoor Recreation Commission, 2002 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - Colorado Rivers, 1987 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - Colorado Roadless Area Inventory, 1985 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - Colorado Roadless Area Review II, H.R. 5487, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 70/13)
    - Colorado Roadless Area Review II-H.R. 5487 Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 70/14)
    - Colorado Roadless Area Review II, H.R. 5487, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 70/15)
    - Colorado Water Project-Dolores Project, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - Colorado Wild and Scenic Rivers-Dolores, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Colorado Wilderness, 1959-2003 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Colorado Wilderness, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - Colorado Wilderness, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - Colorado Wilderness, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Colorado Wilderness Act of 1980, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Colorado Wilderness Act of 1983 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - Colorado Wilderness Act, General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 71/9)
    - Colorado Wilderness Additions, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 71/11-12)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, 1984 (Box-folder 71/13)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, 1993 (Box-folder 71/14)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, 1985, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, S. 2123, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bill, S. 2123-Mallett's Statement Press Releases and Correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Colorado Wilderness Bills and Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Colorado Wilderness Issues, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Colorado Wilderness Legislation, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Colorado Wilderness Legislation, Armstrong, S. 2741, 1980 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Colorado Wilderness Projects, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Colorado Wilderness Proposal, 1983 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Colorado Wilderness Study Act, 2741, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Colorado Wilderness Study Areas #1, 1981 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Colorado Wilderness Study Areas #2, 1982 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - Colorado-Miscellaneous Wilderness Materials, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Columbia River Basin, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 73/1-2)
    - Conference on Wilderness Philosophy and Management, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Congressional and Forest Service Directories, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Congressional Correspondence Regarding Legislation, 1987-2008 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - Congressional Correspondence-General, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Continental Divide Trail Alliance, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Continental Divide Trail-Possible Motorized Use, 2004 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - Correspondence-Timber Interests, 1989 (Box-folder 73/9)
    - Craighead Wildlife-Wildlands Institute, 30 Year Anniversary of the Wilderness Act, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 73/10)
    - Frank and John Craighead, 1985 (Box-folder 73/11)
    - Crazy Mountain Proposed Wilderness Study Area-Gallatin National Forest, 1980 (Box-folder 73/12)
    - Crippen Cabin Removal-Absaroka-Beartooth Wilderness, 2002 (Box-folder 73/13)
    - Bill Cunningham, Articles and Correspondence, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 73/14)
    - Custer National Forest, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 73/15)
    - Kim Davitt, Correspondence, 2006 (Box-folder 73/16)
    - Deep Creek Mountains, 1980 (Box-folder 73/17)
    - Deerlodge Forest Defense Fund, 1998 (Box-folder 73/18)
    - Deerlodge National Forest, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 73/19)
    - Deerlodge National Forest, 1992 (Box-folder 73/20)
    - Deerlodge National Forest-Perry/Pole Environmental Analysis Report, 1981 (Box-folder 73/21)
    - Deerlodge Ranger District, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 73/22)
    - Department of Agriculture News Releases, 1987 (Box-folder 73/23)
    - Department of the Interior News Releases, 1987 (Box-folder 73/24)
    - Dolores River, 1968-1981 (Box-folder 73/25)
    - Dolores River Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 73/26)
    - Draft Environmental Assessment-Missouri National Wild and Scenic River, 1990 (Box-folder 73/27)
    - Draft Montana Wilderness Proposals-Bureau of Land Management, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 74/1)
    - East Pioneers, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 74/2)
    - East Pioneers-Beaverhead National Forest, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Ecosystem Management, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - Electric Peak-Little Blackfoot, 1984 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - Elkhorn Conservation Initiative-Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation, undated (Box-folder 74/6)
    - Elkhorn Mountains, 1965-2005 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Elkhorn Mountains Properties for Sale, 1999 (Box-folder 74/8)
    - Elkhorn Mountains Wildlife Management Area, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 74/9)
    - Elkhorn Mountains Wildlife Management Unit, Clippings, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 74/10)
    - Elkhorn National Wildlife Management Area, 1984-2006 (Box-folder 74/11)
    - Elkhorn National Wildlife Management Area, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 74/12-14)
    - Elkhorn Wilderness, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Elkhorn Wilderness Interview and Miscellaneous Articles, 1982-2005 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Elkhorn Wilderness Study Area, 1981-2001 (Box-folder 75/3)
    - Elkhorn Wilderness Study Area-Helena National Forest, 1976-2005 (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Elkhorn Wildlife Management Area, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 75/5)
    - Elkhorn Wildlife Management Area-Interview, 2005 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - Elkhorn Wildlife Management Area-Mining Correspondence, 1982-1997 (Box-folder 75/7)
    - Elkhorn Wildlife Management Unit, 1981-1997 (Box-folder 75/8)
    - Elkhorn Wildlife Management Unit, 2005 (Box-folder 75/9)
    - Employment Impact-Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act (NREPA)-Dr. Tom Power's Report, 1992 (Box-folder 75/10)
    - Endangered Species Act, 1994 (Box-folder 75/11)
    - Endangered Species Act, 1995 (Box-folder 75/12)